{
	"question_list1": [{
			"number": 1,
			"type": "mult_choice",
			"question": "Which of these tags are NOT related to lists?",
			"answers": [
				"<ul>",
				"<ol>",
				"<li>",
				"<ll>"
			],
			"correct_answer": 3
		},
		{
			"number": 2,
			"type": "true_false",
			"question": "CSS stands for Cascading Style Sheets.",
			"answers": [
				"True",
				"False"
			],
			"correct_answer": 0
		},
		{
			"number": 3,
			"type": "fill_blank_text",
			"question": "The tag for paragraph is ___",
			"correct_answer": "<p>"
		},
		{
			"number": 4,
			"type": "true_false",
			"question": "You can link to a new tab using the target= '_blank' attribute.",
			"answers": [
				"True",
				"False"
			],
			"correct_answer": 0
		},
		{
			"number": 5,
			"type": "fill_blank_text",
			"question": "HTML stands for ____ Text Markup Language",
			"correct_answer": "Hyper"
		},
		{
			"number": 6,
			"type": "text_response",
			"question": "Where is the visible content of HTML code located?",
			"correct_answer": "body"
		},
		{
			"number": 7,
			"type": "fill_blank_text",
			"question": "Inline CSS styling uses the <____> tag",
			"correct_answer": "style"
		},
		{
			"number": 8,
			"type": "mult_choice",
			"question": "Which one of these headings is the largest?",
			"answers": [
				"<h1>",
				"<h2>",
				"<h6>",
				"<h4>"
			],
			"correct_answer": 2
		},
		{
			"number": 9,
			"type": "true_false",
			"question": "There is only one way to style using CSS.",
			"answers": [
				"True",
				"False"
			],
			"correct_answer": 1
		},
		{
			"number": 10,
			"type": "mult_choice",
			"question": "Which one of these is NOT a <table> element?",
			"answers": [
				"<tr>",
				"<td>",
				"<tl>",
				"<thead>"
			],
			"correct_answer": 2
		},
		{
			"number": 11,
			"type": "text_response",
			"question": "What is the correct way to make a textarea input field?",
			"correct_answer": "<input type= 'textarea'>"
		},
		{
			"number": 12,
			"type": "true_false",
			"question": "<br> is used for line breaks",
			"answers": [
				"True",
				"False"
			],
			"correct_answer": 0
		},
		{
			"number": 13,
			"type": "mult_choice",
			"question": "The title of the page should be inside of which section?",
			"answers": [
				"<body>",
				"<head>",
				"<script>",
				"<style>"
			],
			"correct_answer": 1
		},
		{
			"number": 14,
			"type": "text_response",
			"question": "What is the attribute used for images?",
			"correct_answer": "<img>"
		},
		{
			"number": 15,
			"type": "true_false",
			"question": "<ol> is used for unordered lists",
			"answers": [
				"True",
				"False"
			],
			"correct_answer": 1
		},
		{
			"number": 16,
			"type": "fill_blank_text",
			"question": "The ____ attribute is a hint for an expected text field",
			"correct_answer": "placeholder"
		},
		{
			"number": 17,
			"type": "mult_choice",
			"question": "The current <!DOCTYPE> for HTML is ?",
			"answers": [
				"2",
				"3",
				"4",
				"5"
			],
			"correct_answer": 3
		},
		{
			"number": 18,
			"type": "true_false",
			"question": "Javascript is written within a <script> tag.",
			"answers": [
				"True",
				"False"
			],
			"correct_answer": 0
		},
		{
			"number": 19,
			"type": "mult_choice",
			"question": "This is NOT a type of inputs for forms",
			"answers": [
				"radio",
				"checkbox",
				"textarea",
				"placeholder"
			],
			"correct_answer": 3
		},
		{
			"number": 20,
			"type": "fill_blank_text",
			"question": "The tag used within HTML files for Javascript is the <____> tag.",
			"correct_answer": "script"
		}
	],
	"question_list2": [{
			"number": 1,
			"type": "fill_blank_text",
			"question": "Printing a statement in Java can be done using System.__.println(' ');",
			"correct_answer": "out"
		},
		{
			"number": 2,
			"type": "mult_choice",
			"question": "This is NOT a primitive type of Java",
			"answers": [
				"string",
				"byte",
				"char",
				"arrays"
			],
			"correct_answer": 3
		},
		{
			"number": 3,
			"type": "fill_blank_text",
			"question": "There are ___ types of primitive data types relating to numbers",
			"correct_answer": "6"
		},
		{
			"number": 4,
			"type": "text_response",
			"question": "The typical class in Java is not private, but _____",
			"correct_answer": "public"
		},
		{
			"number": 5,
			"type": "mult_choice",
			"question": "These are ways to iterate in Java",
			"answers": [
				"for loop",
				"count by hand",
				"while loop",
				"for each loop"

			],
			"correct_answer": 1
		},
		{
			"number": 6,
			"type": "fill_blank_text",
			"question": "The beginning of the main class of Java is 'public ____ void main'",
			"correct_answer": "static"
		},
		{
			"number": 7,
			"type": "true_false",
			"question": "Java is derived from Javascript",
			"answers": [
				"True",
				"False"
			],
			"correct_answer": 1
		},
		{
			"number": 8,
			"type": "text_response",
			"question": "Java originally was created by this company",
			"correct_answer": "Sun Microsystems"
		},
		{
			"number": 9,
			"type": "true_false",
			"question": "Java is an object-oriented programming language",
			"answers": [
				"True",
				"False"
			],
			"correct_answer": 0
		},
		{
			"number": 10,
			"type": "fill_blank_text",
			"question": "Variables must be defined by their ____",
			"correct_answer": "type"
		},
		{
			"number": 11,
			"type": "mult_choice",
			"question": "Java was released in the year",
			"answers": [
				"2000",
				"1998",
				"1993",
				"1995"
			],
			"correct_answer": 3
		},
		{
			"number": 12,
			"type": "true_false",
			"question": "Java is still owned by Sun Microsystems",
			"answers": [
				"True",
				"False"
			],
			"correct_answer": 1
		},
		{
			"number": 13,
			"type": "fill_blank_text",
			"question": "True or false data types are referred to as _____",
			"correct_answer": "boolean"
		},
		{
			"number": 14,
			"type": "text_response",
			"question": "Constructors are used for what purpose?",
			"correct_answer": "Initializing objects"
		},
		{
			"number": 15,
			"type": "mult_choice",
			"question": "Text variables are known as",
			"answers": [
				"float",
				"text",
				"String",
				"byte"
			],
			"correct_answer": 2
		},
		{
			"number": 16,
			"type": "true_false",
			"question": "Comments are written using \\",
			"answers": [
				"True",
				"False"
			],
			"correct_answer": 1
		},
		{
			"number": 17,
			"type": "text_response",
			"question": "What is the method to get an array, x's length?",
			"correct_answer": "x.length();"
		},
		{
			"number": 18,
			"type": "mult_choice",
			"question": "Comparing values can be done with this operator",
			"answers": [
				"!!",
				"--",
				"&&",
				"=="
			],
			"correct_answer": 3
		},
		{
			"number": 19,
			"type": "true_false",
			"question": "Java 13 is still supported.",
			"answers": [
				"True",
				"False"
			],
			"correct_answer": 1
		},
		{
			"number": 20,
			"type": "fill_blank_text",
			"question": "A method without a return value uses the _____ keyword",
			"correct_answer": "void"
		}
	]
}
